Yeasinur Rahman Rony

♀ Chha 70, North Badda, Dhaka **ⓒ** +8801795183626

m www.linkedin.com/in/yeasinurrony



Career Overview

Structured and adoptable to any work environment with two years of experience in Brand Management, Digital Marketing, Campaign Management, Consumer Engagement

Professional Skills

Brand Management | Content Management | Social Media Marketing | Digital Media Planning | Digital Media Buying | Team Management

Experience

EXECUTIVE - CLIENT SERVICE | ASIATIC MINDSHARE LTD, GOUP M, ASIATIC 360 | JANUARY 2019-PRESENT

- Responsible for the Brand communication of Bashundhara Noodles & Pasta,
 Energypac Electronics Limited, Detos, Spicy Potato Sticks
- Project Supervisor of Detos Rapstar Campaign for New Zealand Dairy
- Conducted Market Research for Bashundara Noodles
- Planned Boishakhi Mela Campaign for Energypac Online Shop

MTO | COOKIE JAR LTD, ASIATIC 360 | JANUARY 2018-DECEMBER 2018

- Responsible for digital communication of Energypac Electronics Limited, Lucy
 Oliva Olive Oil, Giant Agro Farmer's Best
- Responsible for digital media planning and media buying for OBHAI, MeenaClick,
 Biotique Natural, Rancon Automobiles Limited
- Plan and implement social media campaigns
- Supervise content development for social media pages

INTERNSHIP | COOKIE JAR LTD, ASIATIC 360 | AUGUST 2017 - DECEMEBER 2017

Extra-Curricular Activities

- \bullet DIRECTOR | MEDIA AND COMMUNICATION | BRAC UNIVERSITY BUSINESS CLUB | 2013-2016
- VOLUNTEER | CASPER FOUNDATION, BRAC UNIVERSITY | 2016-2017

Hobbies

Music | Reading | Travelling

Education

BBA (MAJOR - MARKETING) | 2017 | BRAC UNIVERSITY | CGPA: 2.80

HSC (BUSINESS STUDIES) | 2012 | GULSHAN COMMERCE COLLEGE | GPA: 4.50

SSC (SCIENCE) | 2010 | MONOHARDI PILOT HIGH SCHOOL | GPA: 4.00

Certifications

DIGITAL GURU GREEN BELT | 2019 | GOOGLE

DIGITAL SALES CERTIFICATION | 2019 | GOOGLE Ads | ID 33509019

GOOGLE Ads FUNDAMENTALS | 2019 | GOOGLE Ads | ID 13212171